<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Catalogue</string>
    <string name="release_label">Release Information</string>
    <string name="language_label">Original Language</string>
    <string name="runtime_label">Runtime</string>
    <string name="genre_label">Genres</string>
    <string name="overview_label">Overview</string>
    <string name="img_photo_content_desc">Poster of the Movie</string>
    <string name="detail_img_item_photo_content_desc">Poster of the Movie</string>
    <string name="main_title">Movie List</string>
    <string name="detail_title">Movie Details</string>
    <string name="language_setting">Language</string>
    <string name="language_option_in" translatable="false">Bahasa</string>
    <string name="language_option_en" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="language_btn">Apply</string>
    <string name="language_title">Language Setting</string>
    <string name="language_message">Language setting applied!</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Movies</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tv Shows</string>

    <array name="data_movie_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_jurassicgalaxy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_incredibles</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_jurassicworld</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ralph</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_blackpanther</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mission</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grindelwald</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_purge</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_tv_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_god</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_title">
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Jurassic Galaxy</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</item>
        <item>Deadpool 2</item>
        <item>Incredibles 2</item>
        <item>Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
        <item>Ralph Breaks the Internet</item>
        <item>Black Panther</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Mission: Impossible - Fallout</item>
        <item>Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald</item>
        <item>A Star is Born</item>
        <item>The First Purge</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tv_title">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Doom Patrol</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Fairy Tail</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>The Flash</item>
        <item>Game of Thrones</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
        <item>Grey\'s Anatomy</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_year">
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tv_year">
        <item>2012</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>1986</item>
        <item>2009</item>
        <item>1999</item>
        <item>2014</item>
        <item>2011</item>
        <item>2014</item>
        <item>2005</item>
        <item>2019</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_release">
        <item>April 23, 2018</item>
        <item>August 20, 2018</item>
        <item>December 21, 2018</item>
        <item>December 1, 2018</item>
        <item>May 18, 2018</item>
        <item>June 5, 2018</item>
        <item>June 22, 2018</item>
        <item>October 1, 2018</item>
        <item>November 5, 2018</item>
        <item>January 29, 2018</item>
        <item>October 30, 2018</item>
        <item>July 27, 2018</item>
        <item>November 16, 2018</item>
        <item>October 5, 2018</item>
        <item>July 4, 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tv_release">
        <item>October 10, 2012</item>
        <item>February 15, 2019</item>
        <item>February 26, 1986</item>
        <item>October 12, 2009</item>
        <item>January 31, 1999</item>
        <item>October 7, 2014</item>
        <item>April 17, 2011</item>
        <item>September 22, 2014</item>
        <item>March 27, 2005</item>
        <item>March 28, 2019</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_language">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tv_language">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Japanese</item>
        <item>Japanese</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>English</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_runtime">
        <item>2h 29m</item>
        <item>1h 16m</item>
        <item>2h 24m</item>
        <item>1h 57m</item>
        <item>2h 1m</item>
        <item>1h 58m</item>
        <item>2h 9m</item>
        <item>1h 52m</item>
        <item>1h 52m</item>
        <item>2h 14m</item>
        <item>2h 15m</item>
        <item>2h 28m</item>
        <item>2h 14m</item>
        <item>2h 16m</item>
        <item>1h 37m</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tv_runtime">
        <item>42m</item>
        <item>60m</item>
        <item>25m</item>
        <item>25m</item>
        <item>22m</item>
        <item>44m</item>
        <item>60m</item>
        <item>43m, 60m</item>
        <item>43m</item>
        <item>50m</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_genres">
        <item>Adventure, Action, Science Fiction</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Science Fiction</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Science Fiction, Animation, Comedy</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Comedy</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Comedy, Animation</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Science Fiction</item>
        <item>Action, Science Fiction</item>
        <item>Family, Animation, Comedy, Adventure</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Fantasy, Science Fiction</item>
        <item>Drama, Music</item>
        <item>Action, Adventure</item>
        <item>Adventure, Fantasy, Family</item>
        <item>Drama, Romance, Music</item>
        <item>Action, Science Fiction, Thriller, Horror</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tv_genres">
        <item>Crime, Drama, Mystery, Action, Adventure</item>
        <item>Science Fiction, Fantasy, Action, Adventure</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Fantasy, Comedy, Science Fiction, Animation</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Science Fiction, Fantasy, Animation, Comedy</item>
        <item>Animation, Comedy</item>
        <item>Drama, Science Fiction, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Drama, Science Fiction, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Drama, Fantasy, Crime</item>
        <item>Drama</item>
        <item>Adventure, Action, Drama</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_description">
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>In the near future, a ship of space explorers crash land on an unknown planet. They\'re soon met with some of their worst fears as they discover the planet is inhabited by monstrous dinosaurs.</item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
        <item>Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a spider-man. When Wilson "Kingpin" Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.</item>
        <item>Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys to save a boy\'s life.</item>
        <item>Elastigirl springs into action to save the day, while Mr. Incredible faces his greatest challenge yet – taking care of the problems of his three children.</item>
        <item>Three years after the demise of Jurassic World, a volcanic eruption threatens the remaining dinosaurs on the isla Nublar, so Claire Dearing, the former park manager, recruits Owen Grady to help prevent the extinction of the dinosaurs once again.</item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.</item>
        <item>Video game bad guy Ralph and fellow misfit Vanellope von Schweetz must risk it all by traveling to the World Wide Web in search of a replacement part to save Vanellope\'s video game, "Sugar Rush." In way over their heads, Ralph and Vanellope rely on the citizens of the internet — the netizens — to help navigate their way, including an entrepreneur named Yesss, who is the head algorithm and the heart and soul of trend-making site BuzzzTube.</item>
        <item>King T\'Challa returns home from America to the reclusive, technologically advanced African nation of Wakanda to serve as his country\'s new leader. However, T\'Challa soon finds that he is challenged for the throne by factions within his own country as well as without. Using powers reserved to Wakandan kings, T\'Challa assumes the Black Panther mantel to join with girlfriend Nakia, the queen-mother, his princess-kid sister, members of the Dora Milaje (the Wakandan \'special forces\') and an American secret agent, to prevent Wakanda from being dragged into a world war.</item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</item>
        <item>When an IMF mission ends badly, the world is faced with dire consequences. As Ethan Hunt takes it upon himself to fulfill his original briefing, the CIA begin to question his loyalty and his motives. The IMF team find themselves in a race against time, hunted by assassins while trying to prevent a global catastrophe.</item>
        <item>Gellert Grindelwald has escaped imprisonment and has begun gathering followers to his cause—elevating wizards above all non-magical beings. The only one capable of putting a stop to him is the wizard he once called his closest friend, Albus Dumbledore. However, Dumbledore will need to seek help from the wizard who had thwarted Grindelwald once before, his former student Newt Scamander, who agrees to help, unaware of the dangers that lie ahead. Lines are drawn as love and loyalty are tested, even among the truest friends and family, in an increasingly divided wizarding world.</item>
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.</item>
        <item>To push the crime rate below one percent for the rest of the year, the New Founding Fathers of America test a sociological theory that vents aggression for one night in one isolated community. But when the violence of oppressors meets the rage of the others, the contagion will explode from the trial-city borders and spread across the nation.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tv_description">
        <item>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow.</item>
        <item>The Doom Patrol\’s members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman abilities — but also left them scarred and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden, the team found purpose through The Chief, who brought them together to investigate the weirdest phenomena in existence — and to protect Earth from what they find.</item>
        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then one day, Goku met a teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the mystical Dragon Balls brought her to Goku\'s home. Together, they set off to find all seven and to grant her wish.</item>
        <item>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn\'t just any ordinary kid, he\'s a member of one of the world\'s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail.</item>
        <item>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin\' Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he\'s not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.</item>
        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to discover he is not the only "meta-human" who was created in the wake of the accelerator explosion — and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it won\'t be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become…The Flash.</item>
        <item>Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Night\'s Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and icy horrors beyond.</item>
        <item>Before there was Batman, there was GOTHAM. Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime world\'s greatest foes, a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordon\'s story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to navigate the multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City, the spawning ground of the world\'s most iconic villains? And what circumstances created them – the larger-than-life personas who would become Catwoman, The Penguin, The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?</item>
        <item>Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle\’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.</item>
        <item>This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
